JORDAN SHARPE

WEB DEVELOPER

647.622.4146 | SHARPEJORDAN@GMAIL.COM | JORDANSHARPE.COM

ABOUT

Hi, I'm Jordan, a web developer based out of Montréal, Canada. I love building clean and responsive sites & apps. I've worked in IT for a decade, most recently as an QA tester/ Technical Support Analyst/interim System Administrator. I'm a quick and determined learner who's apt at finding solutions to whatever problem I encounter.

KNOWLEDGE









HTML JAVASCRIPT CSS REACT DJANGO MYSQL MAC OS WINDOWS LINUX

EXPERIENCE

CASTLE HALL ALTERNATIVES TECH SUPPORT ANALYST: 2019-2023



Supported approximately one hundred users. Wrote JIRA tickets, tested fixes, regression testing, SQL queries. Setup laptops with software and user profiles. Upheld agile methodology through standups and sprints.

BANK OF MONTREAL

IT ASSET ANALYST: 2017-2019



Managed the hardware disposal process for servers, laptops, desktops and printers. Led regular meetings with external vendors to address outstanding records. Used Microsoft Excel daily to track critical data.

MOUNTAIN EQUIPMENT COOP

ADVISOR: 2016-2017



Assisted customers with finding equipment. Participated in optional extra training to learn more about incoming products. Represented the company's mission statement to bring "good times outside".

EDUCATION

GEORGIAN COLLEGE



COMPUTER NETWORKING

DALHOUSIE UNIVERSITY



B.A - ENGLISH